# **IMAM FADHKUR ROKHIM**

6283846902341 | imamfadhkur1@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/imam-fadhkur/ | https://imamfadhkur.github.io/

Magetan, East Java Indonesia

I have an interest in web and android development. For four years, I have learned in online courses and self-study. I have experience in developing android apps with java/kotlin, and web apps with PHP, JS, and Python. in the framework I have learned CI3, laravel, and bootstrap. in my last year, I focused on Python programming. For additional assets of my application, I usually use adobe illustrator and canva.

### **Education Level**

#### Trunojoyo University @ - Bangkalan, East Java Indonesia

Sep 2018 - Mar 2023

Bachelor Degree in Informatics Engineering, 3.56/4.00

- As a teacher in website class at the UKM Creative Computer Club
- · As an assistant in a computer lab
- · Passed PKM-AI on a national scale

#### MAN 2 Magetan - Magetan, Jawa Timur Indonesia

Sep 2015 - Sep 2018

High School Diploma in Science

- · As a class leader for three years continuously
- · As treasurer at OSIS
- · 1st place in the 7k contest

# **Work Experiences**

# STKIP PGRI Bangkalan - Bangkalan, East Java Indonesia

Feb 2023 - Present

Staff KA. Lab

I have tasks to fix if there are any problems in the laboratory, network, or computer on campus.

#### Freelancer - Bangkalan, East Java Indonesia

Aug 2019 - Present

Freelance

Freelance as a web app, mobile app, and design.

### Informatics Engineering, UTM - Bangkalan, East Java

Oct 2021 - Dec 2021

Indonesia

Computer Lab Assistant

Department in faculty of technic, Trunojoyo University

• Practicum assistant in a Web Application Development class.

# LPPM UTM - Bangkalan, East Java Indonesia

Sep 2021 - Dec 2021

Back End Developer

Research Institutions

- Ensure the application can run as it should.
- · Enter the method into the app.
- · Deploy online applications.

#### Informatics Engineering, UTM - Bangkalan, East Java

Jul 2021 - Oct 2021

Indonesia

Full-stack Developer

Department in faculty of technic, Trunojoyo University

• Worked on several projects, one of which was to create a website for a building shop.

### PPI Garam UTM - Bangkalan, East Java Indonesia

Jan 2020 - Dec 2020

Research Assistant

Research Institutions

- · Research assistant
- Administration
- · Data research and materials

### sayalulus.com - Bangkalan, East Java Indonesia

Aug 2020 - Aug 2022

Admin

Startup starting in an online course.

• Organized a website that can be useful or user-friendly for learners.

# Organisational Experience

### Jam'iyah Sholawat Burdah - Magetan, East Java Indonesia

Sep 2022 - Present

Treasurer

· Money management

### youth organization - Magetan, East Java Indonesia

Feb 2022 - Present

Secretary

- Environmental youth
- · Lettering

### OSIS - Magetan, East Java Indonesia

Oct 2015 - Oct 2016

Treasurer

· Trusted as the handling of money

#### PRAMUKA - Magetan, East Java Indonesia

Oct 2016 - Oct 2017

Scout Board Member

· Disciplinary member

### UKM Creative Computer Club - Bangkalan, East Java Indonesia

Oct 2019 - Oct 2020

member of the public relations and information communication division

- · Website manager
- Teacher in website class

# Skills, Achievements & Other Experience

- Patent ❷ (2021): Aplikasi Sistem Rekomendasi Hotel Berbasis Multi-Kriteria Dengan Menerapkan Teknik Normalisasi Dalam Pendekatan Collaborative Filtering
- Soft Skills (2018): As a class leader in 5 years continuously
- Hard Skills ⊚ (2023): Cloud Practitioner Essentials (Belajar Dasar AWS Cloud)

- · Hard Skills (2022): HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP
- Hard Skills (2022): Codelgneter, Laravel
- Hard Skills (2019): Adobe Illustrator and Canva Design
- Projects (2022): Hospital queuing system
- Projects (2022): Hotel Recommendation System
- Webinars Attended (2022): Participant in "The 6th International Conference on Sustainable Information Engineering and Technology (SIET'21)"